TASK:
Select nothing and click Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [1-98], Y: 135 [119-151], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a click_element action, with the argument specifying the element to be clicked as the "Submit" button. This button was identified by its coordinates (X: 50 [1-98], Y: 135 [119-151]) and its visible text label "Submit". The reason for choosing this action was to complete the task as instructed, which was to "Select nothing and click Submit." Since the task did not require any checkboxes to be selected or any text to be entered, the expert directly clicked the "Submit" button without interacting with any other elements on the screen. The "Submit" button was the only element that needed to be activated to complete the task. After the action was performed, the screen status was reported as an Empty Screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the previous interface was no longer displayed, likely due to the submission process leading to a different screen or the application closing."}

