TASK:
Select Naoma, Silva from the scroll list and click Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: control_click_element, arg: {type: tabled_text, X: 68 [2-133], Y: 66 [57-74], text: "Siiva"}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a `control_click_element` action, to select the name "Siiva" from a list of names displayed as tabled text elements on the screen. The argument for this action included the coordinates (X: 68 [2-133], Y: 66 [57-74]) which correspond to the location of the "Siiva" text element (demo_element_2). This action was necessary because the task required selecting multiple names from the list, and using the 'control' key while clicking allows for non-contiguous selection. After this action, the status of the screen showed that the "Siiva" text element was highlighted, indicating it was successfully selected. The highlighting of the text is represented by the attribute `highlighted: True` for demo_element_2 in the after-action screen status, confirming that the action was effective in selecting the name."}
action_3: {name: breakdown, arg: {type: scrollbar_v, X: 142 [134-150], Y: 100 [55-146]}, reason: "The expert performed action_3, which was a `breakdown` action, on the vertical scrollbar (demo_element_1) located at the coordinates X: 142 [134-150], Y: 100 [55-146]. This action was necessary because the task required selecting the name "Naoma" from the scroll list, which was not visible on the screen at the time. The scrollbar is a UI component that allows users to navigate through a list that extends beyond the visible area of the interface. By breaking down the scrollbar, the expert aimed to reveal the sub-components of the scrollbar, such as the up and down buttons and the thumb (the draggable square within the scrollbar that represents the current viewable area), which are used to scroll through the list. After the action, the screen showed the newly visible elements: the up button (demo_element_8) at X: 142 [134-150], Y: 63 [55-71], the down button (demo_element_9) at X: 142 [134-150], Y: 138 [130-146], and the thumb (demo_element_10) at X: 142 [134-150], Y: 87 [75-99]. These elements are part of the scrollbar that allows the user to scroll up and down the list to bring the desired item, in this case, "Naoma," into view."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: down_button (of scrollbar/spinner), X: 142 [134-150], Y: 138 [130-146]}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, a `click_element` action, targeting the down button of the scrollbar (demo_element_9) with coordinates X: 142 [134-150], Y: 138 [130-146]. This action was necessary to scroll down the list and bring the name "Naoma" into view, as it was not visible on the screen before the action. The down button is part of the scrollbar that, when clicked, moves the list content upwards, revealing items that were previously off-screen. After the action was performed, the screen status showed that the scrollbar's thumb (demo_element_10) had moved down slightly to Y: 98 [85-110], indicating that the list had been scrolled. As a result, new tabled text elements became visible: "Naoma" (demo_element_11) at X: 68 [3-133], Y: 111 [102-120], and "Bebe" (demo_element_12) at X: 68 [3-133], Y: 128 [120-136]. Additionally, the previously visible names "Siiva," "Lexi," and "Lia" were no longer visible, confirming that the list had indeed scrolled down to reveal new names."}
action_5: {name: control_click_element, arg: {type: tabled_text, X: 68 [3-133], Y: 111 [102-120], text: "Naoma"}, reason: "The expert performed action_5, which was a `control_click_element` action, with the argument specifying the type as `tabled_text` and the coordinates X: 68 [3-133], Y: 111 [102-120], targeting the text "Naoma". This action was necessary to select the name "Naoma" from the scroll list while maintaining the previous selection of "Siiva". The use of the 'control' key while clicking allows for the selection of multiple, non-adjacent items in a list. After the action, the status of the screen showed that "Naoma" (demo_element_11) was now highlighted, indicating it was successfully selected alongside "Siiva". The coordinates of "Naoma" slightly shifted to X: 68 [3-133], Y: 112 [103-120], which is a common visual feedback indicating that the item has been interacted with. The scrollbar components (demo_element_8, demo_element_9, and demo_element_10) were no longer visible, likely because the focus shifted to the selected text elements, and the scrollbar was not interacted with at that moment."}
action_6: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [1-98], Y: 168 [152-183], text: "Submit"}, reason: "Action_6 was a `click_element` action performed on the "Submit" button, which is identified as demo_element_7. The expert chose this action because the task required the selected names, "Naoma" and "Siiva," to be submitted. The "Submit" button had coordinates X: 50 [1-98], Y: 168 [152-183], indicating its position on the screen, and it was visible, making it the appropriate element to interact with to complete the task. The button was labeled with the text "Submit," which is a common interface element used to finalize a selection or confirm an action. After the action was executed, the screen status showed an "Empty Screen," indicating that the task was completed successfully and the interface had likely transitioned to a different state or screen as a result of the submission, which is typical behavior after such an action in many applications."}

