TASK:
Click on a "text" widget.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 66 [1-130], Y: 66 [55-78], text: "ehH"}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to complete the task of clicking on a "text" widget. The arguments for this action specify the type of element to interact with and its coordinates on the screen. The expert chose to click on demo_element_1, an `input_field` type element with the text "ehH", located at the center coordinates X: 66, Y: 66, with the horizontal range from 1 to 130 and the vertical range from 55 to 78. This element was visible and matched the task requirement of clicking on a "text" widget. The reason for this action was to activate or focus on the text widget by clicking on it. After the action was completed, the screen status was empty, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the interface likely transitioned to a different state or screen as a result of the interaction with the text widget."}

