TASK:
Select UusOQFG, 0Z and click Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 14 [7-22], Y: 60 [53-68]}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a `click_element` action on a checkbox, to select the item associated with the text "UusOQFG." The checkbox that needed to be clicked was identified by its coordinates: X: 14 [7-22], Y: 60 [53-68]. This checkbox was visible and unselected before the action. Clicking this checkbox was necessary because the task required selecting "UusOQFG," and checkboxes are typically used to select items in a list or form. After the action was completed, the checkbox became checked (as indicated by the `checked: True` status), which means the item was successfully selected. Additionally, the text "UusQFG" became invisible, and a new text element "UusOQFG" appeared and was visible, suggesting that there might have been a typo in the original text next to the checkbox that was corrected upon selection, or that the text dynamically updated to reflect the correct item to be selected."}
action_3: {name: click_element, arg: {type: checkbox, X: 15 [8-22], Y: 98 [91-106]}, reason: "The expert performed action_3, which was a `click_element` action on a checkbox, to select the item associated with the text "0Z." The checkbox that needed to be clicked was identified by its coordinates: X: 15 [8-22], Y: 98 [91-106]. This action was necessary because the task required selecting "0Z," and checkboxes are typically used to select items in a list or form. After the action was completed, the checkbox associated with "0Z" (demo_element_5) changed from an unchecked to a checked state (indicated by the `checked: True` status), confirming that the item was successfully selected. Additionally, the text "UusOQFG" (demo_element_12) that became visible after the first checkbox was selected, became invisible again, which might indicate that the visibility of this text element is conditionally linked to the selection state of the first checkbox."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [1-98], Y: 172 [156-189], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, which was a `click_element` action on a button, to submit the selected items as required by the task. The button was identified by its coordinates: X: 50 [1-98], Y: 172 [156-189], and it was labeled with the text "Submit," making it clear that this was the button to complete the form submission process. Clicking the "Submit" button was necessary because, after selecting the required items "UusOQFG" and "0Z" using checkboxes, the task could only be completed by submitting the selections. The "Submit" button (demo_element_11) was visible and located centrally along the X-axis of the screen, spanning almost the entire width of the screen, and positioned towards the bottom on the Y-axis. After the expert performed action_4, the screen status showed an "Empty Screen," indicating that the task was completed successfully and the form with the selected items was submitted, which likely caused the application or webpage to navigate away from the current screen or close the form interface."}

