TASK:
Copy the text in the textarea below, paste it into the textbox and press Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: text_area, X: 55 [2-108], Y: 116 [78-154]}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the text area that needed to be interacted with. The text area is described as having its center at X: 55 and Y: 116, with its edges spanning from X: 2 to 108 and Y: 78 to 154, respectively. This action was necessary because, in order to copy text from a text area, the area must first be focused so that subsequent commands (like 'Select All' and 'Copy') will apply to the correct text. After the action was performed, the status of the text area (demo_element_2) changed to indicate that it was focused, as shown by the addition of the `focused: True` attribute. This focus shift is essential for the next steps in the task, which involve selecting and copying the text within the text area."}
action_3: {name: press_control_A, arg: {}, reason: "The expert chose action_3, which is a `press_control_A` action, to select all the text within the focused text area (demo_element_2). This action was necessary because it is a standard shortcut to highlight all the text in a text field or text area, making it ready to be copied to the clipboard. The text area was already focused from the previous action (action_2), which is indicated by the `focused: True` attribute of demo_element_2. After action_3 was performed, all the text within the text area was highlighted, as indicated by the `highlighted: True` attribute added to the text elements (demo_element_3, demo_element_4, demo_element_5, and demo_element_6). This change signifies that the text "Est viverra", "pretium.", "Malesuada", and "odio. Semper" was successfully selected and ready for the next step, which is copying the text using the `press_control_C` action."}
action_4: {name: press_control_C, arg: {}, reason: "Action_4 was a `press_control_C` action with no arguments, which is a standard keyboard shortcut for copying highlighted text to the clipboard. The expert chose this action because the text within the text area (demo_element_2) was already highlighted by the previous `press_control_A` action, as indicated by the `highlighted: True` attribute on the text elements (demo_element_3, demo_element_4, demo_element_5, and demo_element_6). This action was necessary to copy the selected text "Est viverra", "pretium.", "Malesuada", and "odio. Semper" from the text area so it could be pasted elsewhere. After the action, there was no visible change on the screen because the copying process is an internal action that places the text onto the clipboard without altering the visual state of the screen components. The text remained highlighted in the text area, and the focus stayed on the text area, ready for the next step of pasting the text into the input field (demo_element_1)."}
action_5: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 66 [2-129], Y: 66 [55-76], text: ""}, reason: "Action_5 was a `click_element` action performed on demo_element_1, which is an input field located at the center coordinates X: 66 and Y: 66, with its edges spanning from X: 2 to 129 and Y: 55 to 76. The expert chose this action to focus on the input field, as it was necessary to place the cursor inside the input field before pasting the previously copied text. The input field was initially empty and visible, as indicated by the `text: ""` and `visible: True` attributes. After action_5, the status of the screen showed that the input field (demo_element_1) became focused, as indicated by the addition of the `focused: True` attribute. The text area (demo_element_2) lost its focus, and the highlighted text within it (demo_elements 3, 4, 5, and 6) was no longer highlighted, as the `highlighted: True` attribute was removed, and they were simply visible. This change in focus from the text area to the input field was necessary to proceed with pasting the copied text into the input field."}
action_6: {name: press_control_V, arg: {}, reason: "Action_6 was a `press_control_V` action, which is a standard keyboard shortcut for pasting text from the clipboard into a selected area. The expert chose this action because the input field (demo_element_1), which is a text box where text can be entered, was already focused, as indicated by the `focused: True` attribute. This focus was necessary to ensure that the pasted text would go into the correct location. The input field was located at the center coordinates X: 66 and Y: 66, with its edges spanning from X: 2 to 129 and Y: 55 to 76, and it was initially empty, as indicated by the `text: ""` attribute. After the action, the text "suada odio. Semper" appeared in the input field, which means that the pasting was successful. The text was a part of the content that was previously copied from the text area (demo_element_2), and it was now ready for submission, which would be the next step in the task. The rest of the screen elements remained unchanged, with the text area and other text elements still visible but no longer highlighted or focused."}
action_7: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [1-98], Y: 172 [157-188], text: "Submit"}, reason: "Action_7 was a `click_element` action performed on demo_element_8, which is a button labeled "Submit" located at the center coordinates X: 50 and Y: 172, with its edges spanning from X: 1 to 98 and Y: 157 to 188. The expert chose this action to submit the text that had been pasted into the input field (demo_element_1). The input field was focused and contained the text "suada odio. Semper," indicating that it was ready for submission. Clicking the "Submit" button was necessary to complete the task of copying text from the text area, pasting it into the textbox, and then submitting it. After action_7, the screen status showed an Empty Screen, which indicates that the task was completed successfully and the application likely processed the submission and moved to a different state or screen, which is why no elements were visible anymore."}

