TASK:
Copy the text in the textarea below, paste it into the textbox and press Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: text, X: 18 [5-31], Y: 77 [71-83], text: "eget"}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the text area where the text to be copied is located. The arguments for this action specify the coordinates and the element to interact with. In this case, the expert clicked on the text "eget" within the text area (demo_element_4), which has its center at X: 18 and Y: 77, with the text area's edges spanning from X: 5 to 31 and Y: 71 to 83. This action was necessary to set the focus on the text area so that subsequent actions could be performed on the text within it, such as selecting all text (action_3) and copying it (action_4). After the action was performed, the status of the screen showed that the text area (demo_element_1) became focused, as indicated by the attribute `focused: True`. This focus shift is essential for the next steps, which involve selecting and copying the text from the text area."}
action_3: {name: press_control_A, arg: {}, reason: "The expert chose action_3, which is a `press_control_A` action, to select all the text within the focused text area. This action does not require any arguments because it is a keyboard shortcut that operates on the currently focused element, which in this case was the text area (demo_element_1) with its center at X: 32 and Y: 80, spanning from X: 1 to 63 and Y: 52 to 107. The text area was already focused from the previous action, making it ready for text selection. This action was necessary to highlight all the text in the text area so that it could be copied to the clipboard in the subsequent action. After action_3 was performed, the status of the screen showed that all the text within the text area was highlighted, as indicated by the attribute `highlighted: True` for the text elements (demo_element_3, demo_element_4, and demo_element_5). This visual change confirms that the text was successfully selected, preparing it for copying."}
action_4: {name: press_control_C, arg: {}, reason: "Action_4 was a `press_control_C` action, which is a keyboard shortcut for copying highlighted text to the clipboard. The expert chose this action because, as indicated by the status of the screen before the action, all the text within the text area (demo_element_1) was highlighted (as shown by the `highlighted: True` attribute for demo_elements_3, 4, and 5). The text area was focused, and the highlighted text included "In", "eget", and "vel,". This action was necessary to copy the selected text so that it could be pasted into the input field (demo_element_7) later in the task. After the action was performed, there was no visible change on the screen because the copying process is an internal action that affects the clipboard, not the visual elements on the screen. The text remained highlighted in the text area, and the focus did not change, indicating that the system was ready for the next action, which would involve pasting the copied text into the input field."}
action_5: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 66 [2-130], Y: 124 [113-134], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_5, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the input field where the copied text needed to be pasted. The arguments for this action specify the type of element (`input_field`), the coordinates (X: 66 [2-130], Y: 124 [113-134]), and the initial text content (which was empty, indicated by `text: ""`). The input field (demo_element_7) was located at the center coordinates X: 66 and Y: 124, with its edges spanning from X: 2 to 130 and Y: 113 to 134. This action was necessary to shift the focus from the text area (demo_element_1) to the input field so that the copied text could be pasted into it. After action_5 was performed, the status of the screen showed that the input field became focused, as indicated by the attribute `focused: True`. The text area was no longer focused, and the highlighted text within it was no longer highlighted, as indicated by the absence of the `highlighted: True` attribute for demo_elements_3, 4, and 5. This change in focus was essential for the next step, which involved pasting the copied text into the now-focused input field."}
action_6: {name: press_control_V, arg: {}, reason: "Action_6 was a `press_control_V` action, which is the standard keyboard shortcut for pasting text from the clipboard into a selected area. The expert chose this action because the input field (demo_element_7), which is a space where text can be entered, was already focused and ready to receive text. The input field was located at the center coordinates X: 66 and Y: 123, with its edges spanning from X: 2 to 130 and Y: 112 to 134, and it was empty, as indicated by the `text: ""` attribute. This action was necessary to paste the previously copied text into the input field so that it could be submitted for the task. After the action was performed, the status of the screen showed that the text "l. Molestie. Cras ac" was successfully pasted into the input field (demo_element_7), as indicated by the change in the `text` attribute from empty to "l. Molestie. Cras ac". The input field remained focused, which is necessary for any subsequent actions, such as submitting the form with the pasted text."}
action_7: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [1-98], Y: 152 [136-168], text: "Submit"}}

