TASK:
Copy the text from the 3rd text area below and paste it into the text input, then press Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: text_area, X: 32 [1-63], Y: 133 [117-149]}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the third text area for copying its content. The third text area is identified by its coordinates (X: 32 [1-63], Y: 133 [117-149]), which means it is horizontally centered at 32 pixels with its left and right edges at 1 and 63 pixels respectively, and vertically centered at 133 pixels with its top and bottom edges at 117 and 149 pixels respectively. This action was necessary to select the text within this text area so that it could be copied and pasted into the input field as per the task requirement. After the action was performed, the status of the third text area changed to 'focused: True', indicating that it was successfully selected and ready for the next actions (copying the text). Additionally, the text "Potenti" and "ti" associated with demo_element_13 and demo_element_15 became invisible, while new text elements "Potien" and "tri" appeared as demo_element_18 and demo_element_19, suggesting that the content of the text area may have been scrolled or altered when it was focused, revealing additional or different text."}
action_3: {name: press_control_A, arg: {}, reason: "The expert chose action_3, which is a `press_control_A` action, to select all the text within the focused text area (demo_element_11). This action was necessary because the task required copying the text from the third text area to paste it into the input field. The third text area was already focused from the previous action (action_2), which means it was ready for text manipulation. By pressing Control+A (Select All), the expert ensured that all the text within the text area was selected, regardless of the length or visibility of the text. After action_3 was performed, the status of the screen elements changed to show that the text "Potenti" within the third text area (demo_element_13) was now highlighted, indicating that it was selected and ready to be copied. The text "Potien" and "tri" associated with demo_element_18 and demo_element_19 became invisible, and a new resize handle (demo_element_20) appeared, which suggests that the visual representation of the text area was updated to reflect the selection of the text."}
action_4: {name: press_control_C, arg: {}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, which is a `press_control_C` action, with no arguments because it is the standard keyboard shortcut for copying selected text to the clipboard. This action was necessary because, after selecting all the text in the focused text area (demo_element_11) with the `press_control_A` action, the next step in the task was to copy this text so it could be pasted into the input field (demo_element_16). The `press_control_C` action does not require any arguments as it operates on the currently selected text, which in this case was the text "Potenti" highlighted in demo_element_13. After the action was performed, there was no visible change on the screen because the action of copying text to the clipboard does not alter the visual elements on the screen; it simply stores the selected text in the system's clipboard for later use."}
action_5: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 66 [2-130], Y: 164 [154-175], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_5, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the input field where the copied text needed to be pasted. The input field is identified by its coordinates (X: 66 [2-130], Y: 164 [154-175]), which means it is horizontally centered at 66 pixels with its left and right edges at 2 and 130 pixels respectively, and vertically centered at 164 pixels with its top and bottom edges at 154 and 175 pixels respectively. This action was necessary to ensure that the input field (demo_element_16) was active and ready to receive the pasted text. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed to 'focused: True', indicating that it was successfully selected and ready for the next action (pasting the text). The rest of the screen elements remained unchanged, except for the resize handle (demo_element_20) associated with the previously focused text area (demo_element_11), which became invisible, likely because the focus shifted away from the text area to the input field."}
action_6: {name: press_control_V, arg: {}, reason: "Action_6 was a `press_control_V` action, which is the standard keyboard shortcut for pasting text from the clipboard into the currently focused element. The expert chose this action because, after copying the text from the third text area (demo_element_11) with the `press_control_C` action, the next step was to paste that text into the input field (demo_element_16) which had been focused by the previous `click_element` action (action_5). This pasting action was necessary to complete the task of transferring the text from the text area to the input field. After action_6 was performed, the text "s adipiscing tempus " appeared in the input field (demo_element_16), indicating that the paste operation was successful. The input field's coordinates and dimensions remained the same, with its center at X: 66 pixels and Y: 164 pixels, and its edges spanning from X: 2 to 129 pixels and Y: 153 to 175 pixels. The text area and other elements on the screen remained unchanged, maintaining their visibility and positions as before the paste action."}
action_7: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [1-98], Y: 193 [177-209], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_7, which is a `click_element` action, to interact with the "Submit" button on the screen. The "Submit" button is identified by its coordinates (X: 50 [1-98], Y: 193 [177-209]), which means it is horizontally centered at 50 pixels with its left and right edges at 1 and 98 pixels respectively, and vertically centered at 193 pixels with its top and bottom edges at 177 and 209 pixels respectively. This action was necessary to complete the task of submitting the text that was pasted into the input field (demo_element_16). The "Submit" button (demo_element_17) was visible and needed to be activated to finalize the task. After the action was performed, the screen status was reported as "Empty Screen," indicating that the task was completed successfully and the application or form that was being interacted with had likely processed the submission and moved to a different state or screen, which is why no elements were visible anymore."}

