TASK:
Find the last word in the text area, enter it into the text field and hit Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 66 [1-130], Y: 170 [159-181], text: ""}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a `click_element` action, to focus on the input field where the last word of the text area needs to be entered. The input field is identified as demo_element_10 with coordinates X: 66 [1-130], Y: 170 [159-181], indicating its position on the screen. The input field is empty, as indicated by the `text: ""` attribute, and visible, ready to receive input. This action was necessary because before typing the last word "posuere" into the input field, the field must be active and ready to accept text input. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed to include the attribute `focused: True`, indicating that the input field was successfully focused and ready for text entry, which is confirmed by the cursor appearing in the input field, ready for the next action of typing the word "posuere.""}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "posuere", reason: "The expert performed action_3, which is a `type_text` action with the argument "posuere", to enter the last word found in the text area into the focused input field (demo_element_10). This action was necessary because the task required finding the last word in the text area and entering it into the text field before hitting submit. The last word "posuere" was visible as the text of demo_element_8, located at the bottom of the text area (X: 24 [4-44], Y: 128 [124-133]), indicating it was the final word in the sequence of text elements. After the action was completed, the status of the input field (demo_element_10) changed to include the text "posuere", confirming that the word was successfully entered into the field. Additionally, demo_element_3, which had been previously visible, became invisible and then reappeared as demo_element_12, suggesting a screen refresh or update occurred after the text entry, but this did not affect the completion of the task."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [1-98], Y: 196 [183-209], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert chose action_4, which is a `click_element` action, to interact with the "Submit" button (demo_element_11) on the screen. This button was located at coordinates X: 50 [1-98], Y: 196 [183-209], indicating its central position and the area it occupies on the screen. The text "Submit" on the button clearly indicated its function. This action was necessary to complete the task of submitting the last word "posuere" that had been entered into the input field (demo_element_10). Clicking the "Submit" button is a common way to finalize an input process and trigger the system to process the entered data. After the action was performed, the screen status changed to an "Empty Screen," indicating that the task was completed successfully and the previous interface was no longer displayed, which typically happens when a submission is processed and the user is taken to a different screen or a confirmation message is displayed."}

