TASK:
Find the last word in the text area, enter it into the text field and hit Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: input_field, X: 66 [1-130], Y: 170 [159-181], text: ""}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which was a click on the input field, to activate it for text entry. The input field is described as having coordinates with a center at X: 66 and Y: 170, and it was empty at the time ("text: """). Clicking on this input field was necessary because the task requires entering the last word of the text area into this field. The last word, based on the provided text elements, is "Risus." from demo_element_8, which is part of the visible text in the text area. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed to indicate that it was focused ("focused: True"), which means that the cursor was now active in the input field, ready for text to be typed in. This is evident from the change in the description of demo_element_10, where the "focused" attribute was added and set to True, indicating that the input field was successfully activated and ready for the next action, which was typing the word "Risus" into it."}
action_3: {name: type_text, arg: "Risus", reason: "The expert chose action_3, which is the `type_text` action with the argument "Risus", to fulfill the task requirement of entering the last word of the text area into the input field. The last word "Risus." was identified from demo_element_8, which is a text element with the coordinates X: 61 [3-119], Y: 129 [124-134], and contains the text "purus, volutpat. Risus.". Since the input field (demo_element_10) was already focused, as indicated by its status with the coordinates X: 65 [1-129], Y: 170 [159-181], and the attribute "focused: True", the expert could directly type the last word into it. This action was necessary to complete the task of transferring the last word from the text area to the input field. After the action was performed, the status of the input field changed to show the text "Risus", confirming that the word was successfully entered into the field, ready for submission."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [1-98], Y: 196 [183-209], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert performed action_4, which was a click on the "Submit" button, to complete the task of entering the last word into the input field and submitting it. The "Submit" button is described as having coordinates with a center at X: 50 and Y: 196, and it contains the text "Submit." Clicking this button was necessary because it is the action that triggers the submission process of the entered text. The button was visible and clickable, as indicated by its status in the screen description (demo_element_11). After the action was performed, the task was completed successfully, which resulted in an empty screen, indicating that the application had accepted the submission and had likely moved on to a different state or screen as part of its normal operation."}

