TASK:
Scroll the textarea to the top of the text hit submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: breakdown, arg: {type: scrollbar_v, X: 148 [138-158], Y: 100 [56-144]}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which is a `breakdown` action on the vertical scrollbar (demo_element_3), to reveal the sub-components of the scrollbar. This action was necessary because the task required scrolling the text area to the top of the text, and to do so, the expert needed to interact with the scrollbar's thumb component. The scrollbar's thumb is the draggable part that represents the current viewable area within the scrollable content. By breaking down the scrollbar, the expert could access the thumb and other components such as the up and down buttons, which are essential for scrolling. After the `breakdown` action was executed, new elements appeared on the screen: demo_element_14 (the up button of the scrollbar), demo_element_15 (the down button of the scrollbar), and demo_element_16 (the thumb of the scrollbar). These elements are part of the scrollbar's interactive components, which allow the user to scroll the content up or down by interacting with them. The appearance of these elements enabled the expert to proceed with the task of scrolling the text area by manipulating the thumb (demo_element_16)."}
action_3: {name: drag_mouse_down, arg: {x=148, y=103}, element: {type: thumb (of scrollbar_v), X: 148 [138-158], Y: 104 [96-112]}, reason: "Action_3 was chosen by the expert to initiate the process of scrolling the text area to the top. The action performed was a `drag_mouse_hold_down` at the coordinates x=148, y=103, which corresponds to the location of the scrollbar's thumb (demo_element_16). The thumb is the draggable part of the scrollbar that allows users to control the position of the visible area within the scrollable content. By clicking and holding down on the thumb, the expert prepared to move it, which would result in scrolling the text area. This action was necessary because the task required scrolling to the top of the text area before hitting the submit button. After the action, the screen status showed that the text area (demo_element_1) became focused, indicating that it was the active element on the screen, and the thumb (demo_element_16) remained visible, ready to be moved to scroll the content. The rest of the elements on the screen remained unchanged, maintaining their visibility and positions."}
action_4: {name: drag_mouse_move, arg: {x=148, y=74}, displacement:{x_direction=0, y_direction=-29}, reason: "The expert performed action_4, which is a `drag_mouse_move` action, with the arguments {x=148, y=74}. This action was chosen to scroll the text area to the top by moving the scrollbar's thumb (demo_element_16) upwards. The thumb's initial position was at coordinates X: 148 [138-158], Y: 104 [96-112], and the action moved it to a new position at Y: 74, which is 30 units upwards, indicating a significant scroll towards the top of the text area. This was necessary because the task required the text area to be scrolled to the top before hitting the submit button. After the action, the visible text elements (demo_element_2 to demo_element_11) within the text area became invisible, indicating that they had been scrolled out of view. New text elements (demo_element_17 to demo_element_25) appeared, suggesting that the text area's content had been successfully scrolled upwards, revealing text that was previously not visible. The thumb's new position at Y: 84 [76-91] confirmed the upward movement of the scrollbar, and the rest of the elements related to the scrollbar and the submit button remained visible and unchanged."}
action_5: {name: drag_mouse_up, arg: {}, reason: "Action_5 was a `drag_mouse_release` action, which is the final step in the drag action sequence that began with `drag_mouse_hold_down` (action_3) and continued with `drag_mouse_move` (action_4). The expert had previously clicked and held down the left mouse button on the scrollbar's thumb (demo_element_16) and moved it upwards to scroll the text area to the top. The `drag_mouse_release` action was necessary to release the thumb and complete the scrolling action, ensuring that the text area remained at the top position. This action did not require any arguments because it simply involves releasing the mouse button. After the action, the status of the screen components remained the same as before the action, with the text area (demo_element_1) focused and the scrollbar's thumb (demo_element_16) at the new position (Y: 84 [76-91]), indicating that the text area had been scrolled to the top as required for the task. The visibility of the text elements and other components on the screen did not change as a result of this action."}
action_6: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 50 [1-98], Y: 180 [164-196], text: "Submit"}, reason: "Action_6 was a `click_element` action performed on demo_element_13, which is a button labeled "Submit" with its center located at coordinates X: 50 [1-98], Y: 180 [164-196]. This action was chosen by the expert because the task required scrolling the text area to the top of the text and then hitting the "Submit" button. The "Submit" button was visible and located at the bottom of the screen, separate from the text area and the scrollbar. It was necessary to complete the task, as the previous actions had successfully scrolled the text area to the top, and the final step was to submit the information. After the action was performed, the screen status showed an empty screen, indicating that the task was completed successfully and the application had likely moved on from the current screen as a result of the submission."}

