TASK:
For the user @sergio, click on the "Embed Tweet" button.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: click_element, arg: {type: scrollbar_down_button, X: 150 [143-158], Y: 194 [186-201]}, reason: "The expert chose action_2, which is a click on the down button of a scrollbar or spinner, with coordinates X: 150 [143-158], Y: 194 [186-201]. This action was necessary because the "Embed Tweet" option was not visible on the screen initially, indicating that the content needed to be scrolled down to bring the desired option into view. The down button of a scrollbar is typically located at the bottom of a scrollbar and clicking it scrolls the content of the window downwards. After the action was performed, several elements that were previously visible at the top of the screen, such as the texts "Goldina", "@nibh", "2h ago", and "At porttitor sagittis.", became invisible, indicating they had been scrolled out of view. Meanwhile, new elements appeared at the bottom of the screen, such as the texts "8h ago", "Venenatis in duis ipsum", and "dapibus.", along with their associated icons, showing that the content had indeed been scrolled down as intended."}
action_3: {name: click_element, arg: {type: icon, X: 123 [115-131], Y: 125 [117-133], subtype: "menu"}, reason: "The expert performed action_3, which was a click on an icon element, specifically a menu icon associated with the user @sergio. This action was necessary to reveal additional options related to the tweet by the user @sergio. The menu icon was located at the coordinates X: 123 [115-131], Y: 125 [117-133], and was visible on the screen. Clicking on this menu icon was essential to access the "Embed Tweet" option, which was not initially visible on the screen. After clicking the menu icon, a menu appeared with several options, including "Share via DM," "Copy link to Tweet," "Embed Tweet," and "Mute @sergio." The "Embed Tweet" option, which was the target of the task, became visible on the screen at coordinates X: 96 [52-141], Y: 178 [169-186], along with other related options. This action expanded the menu for the tweet, allowing the expert to proceed with the task by selecting the "Embed Tweet" option in the subsequent action."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: tabled_text, X: 96 [52-141], Y: 178 [169-186], text: "Embed Tweet"}, reason: "The expert performed action_4, which was a click on a screen element of type "tabled_text" with the text "Embed Tweet." The coordinates for this action were X: 96 [52-141], Y: 178 [169-186]. This action was necessary because, after expanding the menu associated with the user @sergio's tweet by clicking the menu icon (demo_element_18), the "Embed Tweet" option became visible within the menu. The "tabled_text" type indicates that the text was part of a list or menu, and clicking on it would trigger the corresponding action, in this case, embedding the tweet. The expert chose this action to complete the task of embedding the tweet for the user @sergio. After the action was performed, the screen was emptied, indicating that the task was completed successfully, and likely a new window or dialog box opened to facilitate the embedding process, which is why the previous screen elements were no longer visible."}

