TASK:
Select -1 with the spinner and hit Submit.

Action History:
action_1: {name: start, reason: "Initiating the task."}
action_2: {name: breakdown, arg: {type: scrollbar_v, X: 144 [136-153], Y: 76 [66-87]}, reason: "The expert performed action_2, which is a breakdown action, on demo_element_3, a vertical scrollbar (spinner) with coordinates X: 144 [136-153], Y: 76 [66-87]. This action was necessary because the spinner controls were not initially visible on the screen, and the breakdown action is used to reveal the sub-components of a complex UI element like a spinner. The spinner is a UI element that allows the user to select a value by clicking on the up or down buttons to increase or decrease the value respectively. By executing the breakdown action, the expert made the up and down buttons of the spinner visible, which are essential for adjusting the value in the input field. After the action, two new elements appeared on the screen: demo_element_5, the up button of the scrollbar/spinner at X: 144 [136-153], Y: 71 [66-76], and demo_element_6, the down button of the scrollbar/spinner at X: 144 [136-153], Y: 82 [76-87], both of which are now visible and can be interacted with to change the value in the input field."}
action_3: {name: click_element, arg: {type: down_button (of scrollbar/spinner), X: 144 [136-153], Y: 82 [76-87]}, reason: "The expert chose action_3, which is a click_element action, to interact with demo_element_6, the down button of the scrollbar/spinner. This button is located at the coordinates X: 144 [136-153], Y: 82 [76-87]. The action was necessary because the task required selecting the value -1 with the spinner, and since the current value in the input field (demo_element_2) was "0", clicking the down button once would decrease the value by 1. The down button is part of the spinner control that allows users to adjust the value in an associated input field by incrementing or decrementing it. After the action was performed, the value in the input field changed from "0" to "-1", indicating that the spinner successfully decremented the value. Additionally, the input field became focused, which means it was ready for further interaction, such as typing or receiving the next action command."}
action_4: {name: click_element, arg: {type: button, X: 52 [4-101], Y: 107 [91-123], text: "Submit"}, reason: "The expert performed action_4, which is a click_element action, on demo_element_4, a button with the text "Submit" located at coordinates X: 52 [4-101], Y: 107 [91-123]. This action was necessary to complete the task of selecting the value -1 with the spinner and then submitting that value. The "Submit" button is a control element that, when activated, triggers the form submission process or finalizes an operation. Since the value -1 was already selected and displayed in the input field (demo_element_2), the next logical step was to submit this value to the system, which is done by clicking the "Submit" button. After the action was performed, the task was completed successfully, and the screen was cleared, indicating that the submission process was executed and the user interface for this task was no longer needed, hence the empty screen."}

